- ObjectiveID: 99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: null
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99B_Yonas_p2
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99B_MSQ_01
  RequiredAchievementId: 99_MSQ_22||(99_MSQ_23&&!99_MSQ_35)
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_objective_title"
  Description: "@99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: Brightwoodv2Arc1
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: null
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99B_Galahad_p2
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99B_MSQ_02
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: PotionHealthT3
  ItemRewardQty: 5.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_objective_title"
  Description: "@99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: Brightwoodv2Arc1
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: null
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99B_Yonas_p5
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99B_MSQ_03
  RequiredAchievementId: 99B_MSQ_02
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT3_Handwear_30
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_objective_title"
  Description: "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_complete_available_response_multi"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: Brightwoodv2Arc1
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_alt
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: null
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99B_Yonas_p5
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99B_MSQ_03
  RequiredAchievementId: 99B_MSQ_02
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_alt_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT3_Handwear_30
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_objective_title"
  Description: "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_complete_available_response_multi"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: Brightwoodv2Arc1
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: null
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99B_Galahad_p4
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99B_MSQ_04
  RequiredAchievementId: 99B_MSQ_03
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT3_Footwear_30
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_objective_title"
  Description: "@99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: Brightwoodv2Arc1
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99B_MSQ_05_findingfort
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 31.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99B_Galahad_p4
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99B_MSQ_05
  RequiredAchievementId: 99B_MSQ_04
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: PotionHealthT3
  ItemRewardQty: 5.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_objective_title"
  Description: "@99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: Brightwoodv2Arc2
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: null
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99B_Galahad_p4
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99B_MSQ_06
  RequiredAchievementId: 99B_MSQ_05
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: PotionFamilyWardLostT5
  ItemRewardQty: 3.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_objective_title"
  Description: "@99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: Brightwoodv2Arc2
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: null
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99B_Sun_p2
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99B_MSQ_07
  RequiredAchievementId: 99B_MSQ_06
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: HoningStoneT3
  ItemRewardQty: 3.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_objective_title"
  Description: "@99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: Brightwoodv2Arc2
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99B_MSQ_08_azothtree
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: null
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99B_Galahad_p6
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99B_MSQ_08
  RequiredAchievementId: 99B_MSQ_07
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: PotionHealthT3
  ItemRewardQty: 10.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_objective_title"
  Description: "@99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: Brightwoodv2Arc2
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99B_MSQ_09_killumberto
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 33.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99B_Galahad_p6
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99B_MSQ_09
  RequiredAchievementId: 99B_MSQ_08 && !Archetype_Mercenary && !Archetype_Warmonger && !Archetype_Tracker && !Archetype_Musketeer && !Archetype_Occultist && !Archetype_Theurgist && !Archetype_Wanderer
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_title"
  Description: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: Brightwoodv2Arc2
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_destroyer
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 33.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99B_Galahad_p6
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99B_MSQ_09
  RequiredAchievementId: 99B_MSQ_08 && Archetype_Warmonger
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_success_destroyer
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_title"
  Description: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: Brightwoodv2Arc2
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_musketeer
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 33.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99B_Galahad_p6
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99B_MSQ_09
  RequiredAchievementId: 99B_MSQ_08 && Archetype_Musketeer
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_success_musketeer
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_title"
  Description: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: Brightwoodv2Arc2
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_mystic
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 33.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99B_Galahad_p6
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99B_MSQ_09
  RequiredAchievementId: 99B_MSQ_08 && Archetype_Theurgist
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_success_mystic
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_title"
  Description: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: Brightwoodv2Arc2
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_occultist
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 33.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99B_Galahad_p6
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99B_MSQ_09
  RequiredAchievementId: 99B_MSQ_08 && Archetype_Occultist
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_success_occultist
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_title"
  Description: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: Brightwoodv2Arc2
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_ranger
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 33.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99B_Galahad_p6
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99B_MSQ_09
  RequiredAchievementId: 99B_MSQ_08 && Archetype_Tracker
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_success_ranger
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_title"
  Description: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: Brightwoodv2Arc2
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_soldier
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 33.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99B_Galahad_p6
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99B_MSQ_09
  RequiredAchievementId: 99B_MSQ_08 && Archetype_Mercenary
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_success_soldier
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_QuestReward_ArcTyp_BW_1hRshield
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_title"
  Description: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: Brightwoodv2Arc2
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_swordsman
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 33.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99B_Galahad_p6
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99B_MSQ_09
  RequiredAchievementId: 99B_MSQ_08 && Archetype_Wanderer
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_success_swordsman
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_title"
  Description: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: Brightwoodv2Arc2
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 34.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99B_Yonas_p9
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99B_MSQ_10
  RequiredAchievementId: 99B_MSQ_09
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: QuestReward_MSQ2_2hFishingPole_Yonas
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_objective_title"
  Description: "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: Brightwoodv2Arc2
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: Soul Trial
- ObjectiveID: 99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_alt
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 34.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99B_Yonas_p9
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99B_MSQ_10
  RequiredAchievementId: 99B_MSQ_09
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_alt_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: QuestReward_MSQ2_2hFishingPole_Yonas
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_objective_title"
  Description: "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: Brightwoodv2Arc2
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: Soul Trial alt
- ObjectiveID: 99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 34.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99B_Galahad_p8
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99B_MSQ_11
  RequiredAchievementId: 99B_MSQ_10
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ringbrightwoodt4
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_objective_title"
  Description: "@99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
